Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Now that's scary.
She's probably using magic
that cuts through physical objects.
It's a simple type of magic,
but I can't see its trajectory.
It's impossible to block all of them, but...
What's the matter? You're not
going to follow up on that?
I might've gone a bit too hard.
Maybe.
The range of your magic is
about five meters, isn't it?
Correct. So, what do we do now?
Are we going to whale on each
other with basic spells again?
No, that won't be necessary.
His magic is devoid of character.
It's underhanded,
for the sole purpose of winning.
The girl fighting Wirbel now
will probably be killed.
Now, then.
A saturation attack?
How can she control so many
attack spells at once?
This is an absurd feat of strength.
It doesn't have a shred of character.
I can't... handle them all.
Sorganeil.
I can't move.
I can't control my mana, either.
It's a powerful binding spell.
If he has this, why didn't
he catch a Stille himself?
Though I suppose it's useless
if he can't find one.
My spell binds those I can see.
As long as I keep looking at you,
you won't be able to move.
I could easily kill you in your current state.
Not only that, but he was holding back.
If he'd truly intended to kill me,
he would've bound me during his initial ambush.
This is your last chance.
Leave the Stille and walk away.
Aw, he's no fun.
And I thought I'd finally
found a fight to the death.
So threatening me into handing over
our Stille was his goal after all.
Wait a minute.
Why do you need to order me to do that?
You could just take the Stille
from me while I couldn't move.
So you need to keep my entire body in view.
No wonder you don't use it
against multiple targets.
You were aiming for my eyes.
That's the logical choice, isn't it?
No. If I were you, I'd go for
the kill and attack the neck.
That would end the fight.
You should've been able to do that.
There were people on the battlefield
who did similar things.
They were all perverts who enjoyed killing.
I guess I should kill you now.
Have you ever killed women
and children before?
You think I haven't?
Huh. What hells have you seen?
Trying to buy time?
Fine. I'll play along.
The Northern Magic Corps are mercenaries
who specialize in fighting demons,
but in times of need, we're mobilized
to fight in wars between nations.
People know exactly what makes
other people weak.
The fiendish act of sending women
and children to war wasn't uncommon.
It wasn't hell.
It's commonplace in the far north.
I see. I've heard enough.
You're not going to kill me?
I think the magic a person specializes in
is strongly related to their life and nature.
A spell that binds your opponent feels like
a way to delay killing them.
I see. That's why you let me buy time, too.
I'm surprised.
Your hands are already drenched in blood,
and yet you still want to remain human.
That's right. I use this time
to prepare myself to kill.
But you know, miss...
Though I may hesitate,
I've always killed everyone I had to.
Later, miss.
Don't move.
You're kidding, right?
You beat Ehre?
I didn't sense her at all.
I'm surprised. You can
completely conceal your mana?
You must be the one who captured the Stille.
We just got lucky.
We happened upon a Stille's roost,
and her master had taught her
a spell that captures a bird.
And you've got a spell that binds anything,
so I guess you just got really unlucky.
Seriously. I've got no luck.
You were fighting Ehre.
What happened to her?
I killed her.
The conditions for passing the first test
are possessing a Stille by sunset tonight
and having all your party members present.
We lost. I'm getting out of here.
I thought you were going to kill me.
I've already failed the test.
Killing you would be unnecessary.
Later.
You can attack me from behind if you want.
You'll just be turning an unnecessary kill
back into a necessary one.
Ms. Übel.
I know.
You're a good liar.
We should go to assist
Mr. Land while we can.
That four-eyes will be fine.
He's quite the pretender.
It's over.
This is impressive.
You turned countless petals into metal
and controlled them precisely
to slip them through my defenses.
But this is your own invention, isn't it?
Spells like that often
neglect the fundamentals.
I always watch and wait when
fighting an opponent I don't know.
I know exactly what your weaknesses are.
I'll probably win.
Talkative, aren't you?
How do you intend to win when
I've ruined your dominant arm?
If you won't surrender,
then I'll take your head off.
I told you, I'm still observing you
before the battle begins.
You're not very good at
detecting mana, are you?
Illusion magic.
It has substance, so strictly speaking,
it's more like a clone.
How long—
Since the beginning,
when the first test started.
I don't trust other people.
Killed her, my ass.
That bitch lied like it was nothing.
Wake up, Ehre.
Out of mana? Pathetic.
Didn't you graduate at the top of your class?
She overwhelmed me with
ordinary offensive magic.
I couldn't block them all.
You don't believe me, do you?
No, I do.
Why'd you attack her head-on like an idiot?
It's not like you couldn't have won.
But if she could pull off this stunt
with ordinary offensive magic alone,
she must be one nasty monster.
Let's go. We'll meet up with Scharf.
Wait. I can't walk.
Oh, fine.
Are you really going to float me
there like an object?
Carry me on your back!
Why am I doing this?
Do you sense Scharf nearby?
He's on the other side of those bushes.
Hey, Scharf. Help me carry...
Wirbel, carry me on your back.
I feel numb and can't move.
Damn it.
Seriously, what the hell is going on?
What's this sound?
Probably the rain.
It's started raining outside the barrier.
It's like my current mental state.
The sun will set in two or three more hours.
The first test will end.
Two of us are out of the fight.
We can't steal anyone's Stille like this.
We're going to fail.
But you're helping us anyway.
You're a nice guy.
I don't mind ditching you
two here, you know.
Please don't abandon us.
Don't cry. You're a man, aren't you?
Is that kindness the reason
you fight demons?
You saved my village, too.
Are you stupid?
I couldn't risk my life for kindness.
People fight for their own desires.
In my case, I had ulterior motives.
I was in love with a girl from my hometown.
Exactly 29 years ago, the demon activity
in the northern lands increased.
She and her entire family
fled to the central lands.
I was a dumb kid.
I decided to show off for her.
I'll kill all those shitty demons.
When I do, come back to this village.
I was only four or five years old.
I don't even remember
her face or name anymore.
What an idiot.
Yeah. I'm an idiot.
Are we sailing back home again?
I get seasick easily.
Want me to introduce you to my grandpa?
Since he's a first-class mage,
we can travel by land to...
Hey, Wirbel.
What is it?
Look.
You can't be serious.
What was all that effort for?
Took long enough for luck to go my way.
Frieren, she's not doing anything.
An elf, huh?
She's a skilled mage.
I doubt Laufen's magic would work a
second time now that she's seen it.
But just once was enough.
We're not trying to kill each other here.
She vanished?
Frieren, the Stille...
She took it, huh?
That's an interesting spell.
It's comfortable inside the barrier
even when it's raining.
Come to think of it, aren't you the proctor
for the second test, Sense?
Looks like you killed a few promising
test-takers again, Genau.
Don't make me laugh.
No promising test-taker would die from this.
Besides, first-class mages
simply have that much worth.
You should know that.
Either way, choosing a target immune to
mana detection for a mage test wasn't nice.
Whether or not they'll catch one
comes down to luck.
This is a battle masquerading
as a competition.
Luck is a skill.
And some test-takers seem to have captured
a Stille without relying on luck.
The sun will set in three hours.
The battle will grow more intense.
Who do you think will survive?
A third will remain.
Denken will be among them.
His skill is comparable
to a first-class mage's.
What's an old man only interested
in wealth and political power
doing getting certified now?
Is he doing it for the privilege after all?
Who knows?
He's getting up there in years.
I'm sure he's got something on his mind.
The spell that girl used
was Jilwer, wasn't it?
That's a folk spell used by a mountain tribe
in the southern lands.
That's right.
What's a Jilwer?
A spell that allows you to move at high speed.
Then the two of you
should've remained hidden.
She could've simply taken
the Stille on her own.
Laufen is still inexperienced.
She left too many traces of mana behind.
You could have easily followed her, Frieren.
You must really find
our presence troublesome.
Well, yes. You know who I am?
There isn't a mage of our generation
who doesn't know that name.
It's my first time seeing
you with my own eyes,
but I knew who you were
as soon as I saw you.
You are Frieren, the mage
from the party of heroes.
Is she famous?
She's a legendary mage.
I knew it might be possible, but...
I guess elves really don't age.
You're challenging me rather openly.
You've been sniffing around us
this whole time, haven't you?
I was expecting something underhanded.
This is plenty underhanded.
While Denken keeps you busy,
I'll kill one of those two kids.
I see.
If we can't pass because we're lacking a
party member, we'll be forced to back off.
Interesting. Try me.
Lawine, he's strong.
I know.
Don't, Richter. All we need
to do is keep them busy.
We can win this fight.
Denken, I thought you were a
more merciless and cold man.
You're an imperial mage, aren't you?
I'm sure you've killed political enemies
more than a couple of times.
I simply don't believe being a first-class mage
is worth killing someone.
I can agree with that.
"First-class mage" is just a title.
It's not that valuable.
You can't be serious.
You mean you took this test without
knowing the privilege that title grants?
Privilege?
More than fifty years ago,
the great mage and founder
of the Continental Magic Association,
Serie, suddenly appeared
to reign over humanity's magic.
She's still searching for mages refined
during the long war against the Demon King.
So she promised to grant a special
privilege to anyone who achieved
the rank of first-class mage.
She will grant them any
one spell they desire.
Serie is a living grimoire who knows nearly
every spell in humanity's history.
She's the closest mage in our world to the
all-knowing and all-powerful Goddess.
You could acquire massive wealth,
cure the gravest of diseases,
or gain overwhelming power.
For mages, to gain whatever spell they want
is equivalent to having a wish granted.
People are simple.
So modern first-class mages are all
monsters who barely seem human.
It's that valuable a privilege.
I see.
This is nonsense.
Denken, people like you who don't care
about the privilege are the minority.
Let's begin.
Denken, keep her busy for one minute.
That's enough time for me
to kill the two of them.
Don't make me say it again, Richter.
They're just kids.
We're simply going to put them
to sleep for three hours.
You can handle looking after
some children, can't you?
Denken.
I'll crush her.
That should be enough.
You old fart.
Bargland.
The young are too hot-blooded.
You inexperienced fool.
What spell do I desire?
The difference between our mana is too great.
But she underestimates us.
Give me a break.
That old man fights rather spectacularly.
I know!
This is Frieren.
In the world of magic, sometimes
the world is turned upside down.